that the other big want to track will be
itc mangalam is standing by with the
expectations
well that's correct you know the stock
has been a smoking hot one this year up
almost 40 percent among the best nifty
performers and the results are expected
to be smoking hot as well largely on a
low base but then again you know
mobility has increased and that will do
well for a lot of their businesses
mostly their cigarette business so what
is the street working with 25 and 22 and
a half percent growth on their top line
closer to the 15 000 crore mark you're
looking at 29 jump in their ebitda that
would mean margins of around 34 and a
half odd percent this compares to 32.7
so they will see a margin expansion as
well and a 35 jump in their net profit
closer to that 4050 crore odd mark what
would lead this performance well the itc
cigarette volume is expected to grow
anywhere between 25 to 28
this remember comes on a low base same
time last year was the second wave off
kovad fmcg margins quarter on quarter
may see a dip of 20 to 30 basis points
primarily on account of the inflation
that we're witnessing the hotel's
business again on a low base will see a
strong revival so that is another thing
that will lead their performance and
strong business performance expected
from both paper as well as the
agribusiness agree business revenues are
likely to grow over 50 percent year on
year the only thing that you know the
street will now watch out for apart from
these numbers is any commentary coming
in on the demerger of the hotels as
sanji puri had told us that now it is
back on the table